
var myFlashcards = [     {question:"printed publication",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/02/reversed-1600-biotechnology-and-organic.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>hall</b></span></a>'},{question:"prior art general level of operability",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/02/reversed-2100-computer-architecture-and.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>elan, beckman, symbol tech</b></span></a>'},{question:"incorporation by reference",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/02/reversed-1700-chemical-materials_22.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>advanced display, seversky</b></span></a>'},{question:"J. rich decision, order of references in rejection doesn't matter",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/03/reversed-3700-mechanical-engineering_12.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>bush</b></span></a>'},{question:"J. Rich case again order of refs doesn't matter",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/03/reversed-1700-chemical-materials_14.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>bush</b></span></a>'},{question:"drawings don't have quantitative values",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/03/reversed-1700-chemical-materials_15.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>hockerson and wright</b></span></a>'},{question:"classification system not important for non-analogous prior art inquiry.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/04/reversed-1700-chemical-materials_09.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>ellis</b></span></a>'},{question:"analogous prior art from same field regardless of problem solved",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/04/reversed-3700-mechanical-engineering.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>klein</b></span></a>'},{question:"in determining non-statutory subject matter will not consider allowed claims in other patents",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/05/reversed-1600-biotechnology-and-organic_07.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>gyurik</b></span></a>'},{question:"(J. Almond 1973) prior art doesn't need constructive or actual knowledge of earlier prior art in order to combine",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/05/reversed-1600-biotechnology-and-organic_10.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>kleinman</b></span></a>'},{question:"(not in mpep) what prior art teaches is question of fact (not law)",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/05/reversed-3700-mechanical-engineering.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>para-ordnance</b></span></a>'},{question:"provisional OK to use as prior art under 102(e)",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/05/reversed-1700-chemical-materials_23.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>Giacomini</b></span></a>'},{question:"'capable of' test requires that prior art be capable of performing the function without further programming.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/06/reversed-1700-chemical-materials_20.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>Typhoon Touch, Microprocessor Enhancement, Ergo Licensing, Telecordia</b></span></a>'},{question:"use of extrinsic evidence OK to show missing material necessarily present in prior art",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/06/reversed-1700-chemical-materials_26.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>Continental Can, Oelrich</b></span></a>'},{question:"prior art has to be publicly accessible",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/07/reversed-1700-chemical-materials_18.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>bayer, cronin, MIT, northern telecom, wyer</b></span></a>'},{question:"no longer in MPEP for analogous art",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/07/custom-search-reversed-2400-networking.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>clay</b></span></a>'},{question:"non-prior art publications ok for sale before critical date",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/07/custom-search-reversed-1700-chemical_27.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>epstein</b></span></a>'},{question:"if applicant says something is prior art it can be used for both 102 znd 103",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/08/reversed-1700-chemical-materials.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>constant</b></span></a>'},{question:"reduction to practice",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/08/custom-search-reversed-tech-center-1600.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>asahi/america and sachs</b></span></a>'},{question:"prior art need not recognize problem solved",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/08/custom-search-reversed-tech-center-2100_24.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>kemps</b></span></a>'},{question:"indicia of publication",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/08/custom-search-reversed-tech-center-1700_27.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>resqnet, katz</b></span></a>'},{question:"prior art must be capable of performing function without further programming",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/08/custom-search-reversed-tech-center-1600_28.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>typhoon techs and microprocessor</b></span></a>'},{question:"if prior art is not analogous then would it have logically commended itself",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/11/clay-dunn-innovention-toys-thibault.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>Innovention Toys, Clay</b></span></a>'},{question:"just because better alternatives exist, prior art not inapt for obviousness",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/11/mouttet-superguide.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>mouttete</b></span></a>'},{question:"for can't pick and choose from prior art excluding what it would have suggested to POSITA",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/11/burroughs-coleman-hybritech-sewall.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>wesslau</b></span></a>'},{question:"related art is not prior art if inventor's own work, even if labelled PRIOR ART",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/11/constant-reading-and-bates.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>Constant, Reading &amp; Bates</b></span></a>'},{question:"printed publication must be disseminated",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/11/leshin-superguide-syest-wyer.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>wyer</b></span></a>'},{question:"drawings merely illustrative",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/12/aristocrat-katz-interactive-olson-reuter.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>olson</b></span></a>'},{question:"if prior art adds a step to 'consisting essentially of' claim, applicant has to prove step materially changes characteristics of invention",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/12/de-lajarte-hoffman.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>De Lajarte, hoffman</b></span></a>'},{question:"conclusory statements in 131 decs not enough to establish reduction to practice",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2012/12/amhil-asahiamerica-bell-and-howell.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>asahi</b></span></a>'},{question:"in jepson claims preamble is admitted prior art",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/01/comark-free-motion-sjolund-tandon.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>sjolund</b></span></a>'},{question:"prior art structure must be able to perform function without further processing",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/02/mayo-microprocessor-perkinelmer-typhoon.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>typhoon touch, microprocessor enhancement</b></span></a>'},{question:"plant genetics enabling prior art POSITA must be able to grow and cultivate the plant",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/02/elsner-legrice.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>legrice and elsner</b></span></a>'},{question:"no matter how old prior art, still have to show tried and failed to solve problem",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/02/ccs-mcguire-phillips.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>mcguire</b></span></a>'},{question:"failure is evidence of nonenabling, not attempting is not",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/02/donohue-omega-santarus.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>donohue</b></span></a>'},{question:"drawings not to scale, merely illustrative",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/03/chu-nash-olson.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>nash, olson</b></span></a>'},{question:"interference estoppel",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/03/angstadt-deckler-hogan.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>deckler</b></span></a>'},{question:"reference relied on that expressly anticipates or makes obvious presumed operable",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/03/donaldson-aristocrat-wms-lindberg-sasse.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>sasse</b></span></a>'},{question:"prior art drawing can be used even though feature unexplained",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/04/aslanian-in-re-merck-keller-klosak.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>aslanian</b></span></a>'},{question:"drawings can be used for all they disclose, no matter whether explained in spec",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/05/hewlett-packard-aslanian.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>aslanian</b></span></a>'},{question:"for prior art no ipsissimis verbis test, identity of terminology is not required",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/05/bond.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>bond</b></span></a>'},{question:"drawings can be cited even though feature unexplained",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/06/aslanian-baum-caveney.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>aslanian</b></span></a>'},{question:"drawing evaluated on basis of what it reasonably discloses to POSITA",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/06/aslanian-baum-caveney.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>baum</b></span></a>'},{question:"to qualify as printed publication under 102 has to be sufficiently accessible to public",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/07/renishaw-lister.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>lister</b></span></a>'},{question:"to be publically accessible POSITA can locate it and PTO must prove",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/08/lister-cronyn-klopfenstein-cordis-wyer.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>lister, cronyn, klopfenstein, cordis, wyer, hall</b></span></a>'},{question:"on sale bar needs commercial offer for sale and invention ready for patenting",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/08/pfaff-atlanta-netscape.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>pfaff, atlanta, netscape</b></span></a>'},{question:"copyright registration insufficient evidence of public accessibility",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/08/lister.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>lister</b></span></a>'},{question:"trade secret overcomes presumption of general right to inspect and copy public records and documents",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/08/psystar.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>psystar</b></span></a>'},{question:"prior art structure can't be modified to perform required function",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/08/typhoon-touch.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>typhoon touch</b></span></a>'},{question:"statements by applicant during prosecution identifying certain matter not the work of inventor as 'prior art' is an admission",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/12/riverwood-nomiya-garfinkel.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>riverwood, nomiya, garfinkel</b></span></a>'},{question:"generic structural disclosure sufficient for 'controller'",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/12/typhoon-microprocessor-ergo-telcordia.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>ergo, telcordia</b></span></a>'},{question:"prior art structure has to be 'capable of' performing the function without further programming",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2013/12/typhoon-microprocessor-ergo-telcordia.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>typhoon, microprocessor</b></span></a>'},{question:"to claim priority to foreign app have to properly cite it",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/01/envirco-kemco-b-braun-donaldson.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>encyclopaedia</b></span></a>'},{question:"for analogous art 2 steps, same field or reasonably pertinent to problem",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/01/envirco-kemco-b-braun-donaldson.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>innovention, wyers, ksr klein bigio</b></span></a>'},{question:"if applicant challanges enablement of printed publication cited by examiner must review evidence",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/02/morsa-antor-media.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>morsa, antor media</b></span></a>'},{question:"analogous art: same endeavor, if not, reasonably pertinent to problem inventor is involved with",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/02/bigio-chaganti.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>bigio, chaganti</b></span></a>'},{question:"sound basis for believing products of applicant and prior art are the same, applicant has burden to show not",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/04/best.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>best</b></span></a>'},{question:"posting to newsgroup is printed publication under 102, but posting to ftp server without more isn't",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/06/suffolk-sri.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>suffolk, SRI</b></span></a>'},{question:"For a reference to be reasonably pertinent, it must logically have commended itself to an inventor",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/06/icon-clay.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>ICON, clay</b></span></a>'},{question:"arguments based on mere measurement of the drawings [are] of little value.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/08/chitayat-nautilus-energizer-holdings.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>chitayat</b></span></a>'},{question:"use of prior art irrelevant, the statute authorizes patenting of machines not their uses.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/09/kunzmann-kollman-lebounty-dwight-lloyd.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>labounty, dwight &amp; lloyd</b></span></a>'},{question:"apparatus claims must be distinguished from the prior art in terms of structure rather than function",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/09/schreiber-hewlett-packard-boehringer.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>schreiber</b></span></a>'},{question:"if patents and prior art easily understandable, one cannot argue an unnecessary fact material to POSITA",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/10/chore-time.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>chore-time</b></span></a>'},{question:"prior art can anticipate even though it describes claimed subject matter using different terms",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/10/schaumann.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>schaumann</b></span></a>'},{question:"J.Rich A reference must be considered for everything it teaches, not limited to invention it is describing",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2014/12/ewp.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>EWP</b></span></a>'},{question:"reference that describes intermediate of structure can be prior art",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/01/alice-mayo-mullin-herbert.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>mullin, herbert</b></span></a>'},{question:"if prior art not in field then must be reasonably pertinent ie common sense POSITA wld look there",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/01/deminski-wood-oetiker.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>deminski, wood, oetiker</b></span></a>'},{question:"if prior art not in field then must be reasonably pertinent ie common sense POSITA wld look there",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/01/deminski-wood-oetiker.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>deminski, wood, oetiker</b></span></a>'},{question:"mere qualifying remark in prior art not enough to lead POSITA in divergent direction for teaching away",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/01/gordon-galderma.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>galderma</b></span></a>'},{question:"for 103 fact prior art could be modified not enough, unless suggestion of desirability of modification",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/01/gordon-galderma.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>gordon</b></span></a>'},{question:"mere qualifying remark in prior art not enough to lead POSITA in divergent direction for teaching away",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/01/gordon-galderma.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>galderma</b></span></a>'},{question:"for 103 fact prior art could be modified not enough, unless suggestion of desirability of modification",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/01/gordon-galderma.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>gordon</b></span></a>'},{question:"typhoon touch - 'capable of' test requires prior art structure capable of performing function w/o further programming",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/01/playtex-york-prod.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>typhoon touch</b></span></a>'},{question:"inventor’s testimony of constructive reduction to practice must be corroborated by evidence",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/01/ntp.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>NTP</b></span></a>'},{question:"100 year old patent OK for 103 combination",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/02/morris-wright.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>wright</b></span></a>'},{question:"agency must give effect to unambiguously expressed intent of Congress",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/03/chevron.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>chevron</b></span></a>'},{question:"unless ref discloses within four corners not only all limitations but also arranged as in claim no 102",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/03/net-moneyin-hockerson-halberstadt-alza.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>net moneyin</b></span></a>'},{question:"to anticipate, prior art need only meet inherently disclosed limitation to extent the patented method does.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/05/kuhle-king.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>king</b></span></a>'},{question:"non-functional descriptive material may not be relied on for patentability",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/04/king-ngai-gulack.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>ngai, gulack</b></span></a>'},{question:"new set of instructions cannot distinguish kit from prior art",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/04/astrazeneca-ngai-king.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>astrazeneca, ngai, king</b></span></a>'},{question:"presumption prior art enabling overcome if process making composition unknown at time of invention",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/06/paulsen-intellicall-sasse-hoeksema.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>sasse, hoeksema</b></span></a>'},{question:"putting a fig in the background section and describing it as conventional makes it prior art.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/06/riverwood-constant.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>riverwood, constant</b></span></a>'},{question:"If a prior art structure is capable of performing a claimed intended use, then it meets the claim.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/07/hewlett-packard-schreiber.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>schreiber</b></span></a>'},{question:"If a prior art structure is capable of performing a claimed intended use, then it meets the claim",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/07/hewlett-packard-schreiber.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>schreiber</b></span></a>'},{question:"if prior art accessibility proved, no requirement public actually received information",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/08/constant-enhanced-security.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>constant, enhanced security</b></span></a>'},{question:"patent drawings not relied upon does not mean things they show are disregarded",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/08/mclaughlin-mraz-hockerson-halberstadt.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>mraz, hockerson-halberstadt, wilson</b></span></a>'},{question:"A prior art reference cannot anticipate if not enabled, burden on applicant",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/08/antor-media-amgen-baldwin-graphic.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>antor media, amgen</b></span></a>'},{question:"even if ref discloses inoperative device, prior art for all that it teaches",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/10/reading-and-bates-beckman-symbol-tech.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>reading and bates, beckman, symbol tech</b></span></a>'},{question:"question is whether inventor wld look to this particular art to solve the particular problem at hand.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/11/clay-circuitcheck.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>circuitcheck</b></span></a>'},{question:"ref reasonably pertinent if logically wld have commended itself to inventor's attention in considering prob",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/11/clay-circuitcheck.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>clay</b></span></a>'},{question:"Structural similarities and functional overlap can show prior art ref reasonably pertinent to invention",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/11/bigio-ellis.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>ellis</b></span></a>'},{question:"analogous art has two separate tests; same field or reasonably pertinent to same problem",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/11/bigio-ellis.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>bigio</b></span></a>'},{question:"statement by applicant certain matter is prior art admission matter is prior art for all purposes",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/11/constant-nomiya.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>constant, nomiya</b></span></a>'},{question:"must give clear explanation of exhibits used to antedate a reference pointing out what facts established",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/11/borkowski.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>borkowski</b></span></a>'},{question:"[A]n accidental disclosure, if clearly made in a drawing, is available as a reference.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/12/wagner-mrazseid.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>mraz, seid</b></span></a>'},{question:"drawings can be used as prior art, only if the prior art features are clearly disclosed by the drawing.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2015/12/wagner-mrazseid.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>wagner</b></span></a>'},{question:"ref used for all it realistically teaches, not limited to disclosures in specific illustrative examples.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/01/syntex-beckman-chapman.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>Chapman</b></span></a>'},{question:"What ref teaches POSITA not limited to what it specifically 'talks about' or is 'mentioned' or 'written'",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/01/syntex-beckman-chapman.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>syntex</b></span></a>'},{question:"POSITA able to read a ref for all that it teaches, not limited to its explicit text preferred embodiment",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/01/syntex-beckman-chapman.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>Beckman</b></span></a>'},{question:"if prior art reflects appropriate level of skill absence of specific findings not reversible error",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/02/chore-time-okajima-litton.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>okajima, litton</b></span></a>'},{question:"[a] machine is a concrete thing, consisting of parts, or of certain devices and combination of devices.",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/02/burr-schreiber-hallman.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>burr</b></span></a>'},{question:"cts shld consider prior art refs in entirety including those portions that would argue against obviousness",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/03/panduit.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>panduit</b></span></a>'},{question:"Wikipedia unreliable (l) not peer reviewed; (2) authors unknown; (3) anyone can contribute",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/03/bing-shun-badasa.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>bing shun, badasa</b></span></a>'},{question:"131 dec. OK to establish a prior invention date, no mandate for some heightened independent corroboration",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/03/ntp.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>NTP</b></span></a>'},{question:"capable of test req. prior art capable of performing function w/o more programming",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/04/typhoon-touch-microprocessor.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>typhoon touch, microprocessor</b></span></a>'},{question:"dissemination and public accessibility key to legal determination whether prior art ref published",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/04/cronyn-constant.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>cronyn, constant</b></span></a>'},{question:"Later publications may be used as evidence of the state of the art existing on filing date of an application",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/07/life-techs-hogan.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>hogan</b></span></a>'},{question:"adequate support in the prior art for changing structure of prior art compound for 103",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/07/procter-gamble-grabiak-ruskin.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #38761d;"><b>procter &amp; gamble, grabiak</b></span></a>'},{question:"refs published after filing date of appellant’s application not evidence of subject matter known to POSITA",answer:'<a href="http://www.ptab.us/2016/12/gunn2-seachange.html" style="color: #3366ff;"><span style="color: #e69138;"><b>gunn2</b></span></a>'}
     ];
